<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>
   
      <title>twitter.com/dipomajekodunmi/</title>
   
   <link>https://twitter.com/dipomajekodunmi</link>
   <description>A collection of articles, tutorials, how-to guides, useful resources and more from my experience learning and implementing ProcessMaker Workflow and BPM solutions.</description>
   <language>en-uk</language>
   <managingEditor> 'dipo Majekodunmi</managingEditor>
   <atom:link href="rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
   
	<item>
	  <title>Are you still running around to get approvals?</title>
	  <link>//are-you-still-running-around-to-get-approvals</link>
	  <author>'dipo Majekodunmi</author>
	  <pubDate>2017-09-01T20:37:01+01:00</pubDate>
	  <guid>//are-you-still-running-around-to-get-approvals</guid>
	  <description><![CDATA[
	     <p>The testimonial below recently posted on the <a href="http://www.processmaker.com/">ProcessMaker website</a> succinctly captures one of the primary benefits of using a Business Process Management solution for your business.</p>

<blockquote>
  <p>“ProcessMaker has helped us improve the efficiency of our employees. Instead of running around to get approvals, we now have a software based process management.” ~ CEO, Renaissance Construction</p>
</blockquote>

<h4 id="your-employees-time-isvaluable">Your employees’ time is valuable</h4>

<p>As every business owner or manager knows, your business is only as good as its people — your employees. And they do not come cheap. Employee wages and benefits make up a significant portion of the operating expense of your business and you would want to ensure you are getting the best value for your money.</p>

<p>However, this is not always the case, as more often than not, employees spend valuable time running after supervisors and bosses to get approvals before they can get their work done. This can range from authorising an expense or releasing an item from inventory.</p>

<p>These little minutes and sometimes hours spent tracking down a boss can quickly add up to significant amount of <strong>time spent being busy instead of productive</strong>. These wasted bits of time are even compounded when the “approver” is located in a different office or is away on a business trip. Forms are printed, scanned, emailed, printed, signed, scanned, emailed and then printed just to get a consent to get work done.</p>

<h4 id="help-them-with-automation">Help them with automation</h4>

<p>By adopting a Business Process Management solution like ProcessMaker, employees simply log in to the system and fill out the necessary form. Once submitted, the form is routed to the designated approver based on predefined business rules.</p>

<p>The approver also logs in to the system, reviews the form and approves or rejects the request. If further clarification is required, the supervisor/manager and employee can add case notes to the form and have the other party notified via email. This eliminates sending the form back and forth.</p>

<p>It even gets better. For employees and approvers on the go, ProcessMaker comes with mobile apps for both iOS and Android allowing your employees get work done on the go. The mobile apps also come with push notifications, so they are notified instantly when a task requires their attention.</p>

<p>This is just one benefit of automating your forms-based approval workflows. You save your employees valuable time, making them more productive and efficient. And that time spent running around to get approvals can be used to create more value for your business and ultimately more profits — after all, the business of business is to make money.</p>

<p><em>This post first appeared on <a href="https://medium.com/dipolediamond/are-you-still-running-around-to-get-approvals-a93ce6d4097d">Medium</a> on December 16, 2016.</em></p>

	  ]]></description>
	</item>


</channel>
</rss>
